Hello. This is Halikurumi.
Sorry, sorry. One more time.
One more time.
I am Oribe.
I am Kika Taki.
Nice to meet you.
It's been too long since we've met, and we have too much to talk about,
I'll give you a refill.
We've only talked about cheese, so there's still a lot to talk about.
That's for sure.
The second part was about cheese,
So we have a lot more to talk about,
I'm going to have another one.
Thank you very much.
So, what are we talking about?
You said you wanted a refill,
What are you talking about?
Is he into anything lately?
He watches cartoons from time to time.
Every now and then?
Is he really watching all of them?
He can't watch everything.
He narrows it down at the beginning, right?
I'll narrow it down.
I'm serious about watching anime.
Well, I'll watch some,
I narrow it down and narrow it down and narrow it down.
But then I narrow it down and narrow it down,
Lately,
I've been into watching Jump's full-length anime.I'm into watching Jump feature-length anime.
You're into that as a genre?
Genre, yes.
First, I watched One Piece back from the beginning,
And then, during this time.
Since the end of last year.
Anime.
Anime?
Yeah.
A thousand and one episodes,
What?
What? Scary.
That's too bad.
Huh? Scary.
I'm not scared.
I thought that was impossible for humans.
It's not impossible.
I saw it about three months ago.
What?
You haven't slept, have you?
Isn't that good?
I'm scared.
I'll control it for the duration of the show.
Which period?
When there is a play or something.
But on other days, when there's nothing going on, I watch a little more than a couple of shows in one day,
You don't eat, do you?
Yes, I am eating.
You watch while eating.You're watching while you eat.
You're watching while you eat.
And watching One Piece,
After JUMP was over, I thought it was interesting.
I thought, "That's just like JUMP,
Next, I want to watch Hiroaka,
Then I want to watch Hunter Hunter.
From the first.
It's the best.
How many episodes of Hunter Hunter are there?
A little over 150.
That's still a lot.
It was over in an instant. It was too much fun.
What?
It was over in an instant, not even a month.
It didn't even last a month. 150.
It's been a month. I saw it in about half a month.
What was that?
I'm already thinking about doing another round.
I think I can do it.
You can do it.
Yes, you can.
If you were to rank the previous animations.
That's a bit of a decision.
I'm sorry.
Eh... I'll watch it.
Seriously?
I can't do it in half a month.Not in half a month, though.
I'm seriously losing money. Who hasn't seen this.
Ew.
I thought I was seriously losing money.
I don't know. I want to see it.
That being said.
I never said it wasn't interesting.
I've been watching it for a long time.
I've been watching it for a long time. Because.
Maybe I'll watch it.
I really want to watch it when I have an add-on. Movies and stuff.
The movie "Black Clover" is also interesting.
Already finished?
We're going to start talking about Black Clover, too.
It's been a while since we've talked like this,
I've been snotty,
You talk so much about anime.
I only watch anime. Because right now.
You only listen to the voices of the cartoonists?
Yes, I do. That's right.
Yeah. That's serious.
That's not good.
It's bad, isn't it?
It's getting worse.
Black Clover has 170 episodes.
That's a long time. That's long too.
We're only talking about another anime.
See you next time.
Okay, see you next time. Let's talk about Chukun-chan.
What's that?What is that?
He's never going to come out of the tension he's been in up until now.
No, he really hasn't changed.
He hasn't changed at all. He really hasn't changed at all.
I want to do another event.
I want to. Don't you want to get together?
Yes, I do. I do.
We can get together and sing some songs and stuff.
The five of us together.
To be honest, I really haven't danced at all,
It's hard.
I don't think I can dance even one song.
No one is dancing right now.
We used to be takoyaki potatoes.
I don't even sing that much.
I don't get a chance to sing.
I don't dance while singing.
Not on a daily basis.
If it was a hobby, I'd know. I might be doing it.
But you don't do it. Definitely.
I'm not doing it.
Is there anything you want to do? A job you want to do?
What do you want to do?
I'd like to be a voice actor for video games.
That sounds great.
I wonder if it's good.
I mean, there's no one this passionate about it.
But I haven't learned anything at all. I'm a voice actor.
There it is, this.
If Karen is in charge, her love for the work is a sign of greatness.If Karen is in charge, her love for the work is a great letter.
I think I would tweet about it every day. I think I will tweet every day.
I'll tweet every day, and I'll definitely celebrate her birthday.
I'll buy a cake.
My character's cake.
He's a good voice actor.
I'll definitely pull the gacha.
I'll keep on pulling until I hit it.
I'll pull until I hit it.
I want to buy one.
What's your name?
Well, I don't know.
Something I want to do.
I want to do something like this, or I want to challenge myself.
Radio!
Oh!
I did radio.
I think it's definitely good.
I love radio,
I listen to it a lot,
It's difficult because it's just talking.
It's difficult because it's just a voice,
I'd like to give it a try.
Radio is fun.
It's fun, isn't it?
It's a lot of fun, so you should definitely do it.
I'm sure you can do it.
Do it.
Do it. Then you can do it.Do it. Then you can do it.
I can do it.
Why not?
Please, people who can't listen to the radio.
Please. I'd love to.
In Osaka or Tokyo.
I'll go to Aomori and other places.
I really want to go to Aomori.
Suddenly.
I'm sorry for mentioning Aomori.
I've never been to Aomori. Have you been to Aomori? Aomori.
Yes, I have.
I tried talking to him.
I went there with my family.
I haven't been to Tohoku much.
I've been to Miyagi, though.
Wouldn't it be great if we could go back to Tohoku for the event?
Yes, it would be. I'd like to go with everyone.
I haven't been to many places, like the special skills level.
I haven't been.
I had a lot of fun in Aomori.
What did you do? In Aomori.
Well, I made a lamp out of a gourd with a hole in it.
What? But it sounds fun. It was fun.
It was fun.
Also, I made a cockscomb out of that Keiryuu bamboo in Aomori.
It was a lot of fun.
And the food was delicious.
Of course it was.
The rice is delicious.The rice is delicious.
Yes, it is.
And the drinks are good, too.
It's all like a school trip.
Gourd lamps.
They're making gourd lamps.
She said she was about to cry again.
You should have made her laugh.
When the five of us went on the trip, we probably had different ideas of where we wanted to go.
We couldn't even agree on where to go out for dinner.
We really don't agree.
We probably all had different ideas of where we wanted to go, but in the end,
Well, what? We'll decide without any fistfights or anything.
That's true. What are we going to do? What should we do about that in a fight?
It seems like it's going to be a quick decision.
When we live together, we always talk about what we're going to do for dinner,
We never come to a consensus, so the final decision is that Saki will look at the supermarket and decide what she wants to cook.
In the end, it is the dish you want to make, but if it is a good ingredient, you decide to use it.
And then the decision is made.
But when it came to going out for fun, someone would suddenly make a proposal and everyone would agree to it,
So we didn't split on that.
It didn't really split. We didn't break up about going out for fun.
But the meal really cracked.
It cracks.
It really cracks.
There are definitely three patterns that crack.
It cracks. It definitely breaks.
The manager asked me to make it one.
So we all play rock-paper-scissors-scissors to decide.
Whoever wins the most gets to decide.Whoever wins the most gets to decide.
Oh, yes.
So, in Nagoya, we had kishimen, miso katsu (pork cutlet), and ramen,
I definitely wanted to have either kishimen or miso katsu,
I remember that one of us who chose ramen won and we all ate ramen together.
And guess who it was? That one person.
Who?
Saku-chan.
Isn't he strong?
He's strong.
He is.
The ramen was good, too,
It's delicious.
When I go to Nagoya, I eat ramen with kishimen and miso katsu.
Regular ramen.
Kishimen.
I said it was 2-2-1.
That's right.
2-2-1, and I said kishimen.
I had kishimen, too.
And miso katsu, miso katsu ramen.
Ramen took my ramen.
That's right. It's so funny, isn't it?
But in that case, we played fair rock-paper-scissors-scissors.
So we really had different tastes in food.
We used to do it all the time.
We did.
You've done well so far.
You did a good job, dinner.
I'll decide.I'll decide.
Well, well, well, but it's been a long time and it was fun.
I'm relieved to see that nothing has changed.
No, really.
He hasn't changed at all.
I don't know, his love of anime has gotten a little bit worse.
He was getting worse.
Terrible.
Terrible. Isn't it terrible?
Thank you very much. I'm sorry.
Amazing. You're still a nerd.
It's bad, isn't it?
I think I need to get out of the house.
No, really, let's take him out for a bit.
Thank you very much.
I want to go to various places with everyone again.
I want to go. I want to go drinking.
I want to go.
Let's really go.
I want to go drinking first.
I want to go.
Yeah, I want to go.
We don't go out much, do we? All of us. I've been, but not that often. I've always wanted to go.
Let's go. Let's go.
We've all been to the Corona Disaster since we came of age. That's right.
It was a hard time, so I'd like to have a good time with everyone. I'd like to.
It's a little bit nostalgic, isn't it? Yes, it is.
It makes me nostalgic. I miss it so much.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Thank you for being a good friend to me even now. Yes, I do.Thank you for still being a good friend. Yes, I am.
I will watch Hunter Hunter. Oh, please watch. Next.
Um, um, I'll see it at the gimme.
150.
If I work hard, I might be able to see it.
The theme song is all the same.
What the hell kind of information is that?
Oh, the remake.
The details are the same.
So thank you all for watching.
Bye bye.
I'm Harikudomi.
I was Yoshin Iibushi.